const questions = [
    {
        question: "Which player has won most trophies in football?",
        correct: 2,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Lionel Messi' },
            { 1: 'Cristiano Ronaldo' },
            { 2: 'Dani Alves' },
            { 3: 'Daivd Beckhm' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Who has the most followers on Instagram?",
        correct: 1,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Cristiano Ronaldo' },
            { 1: 'Ariana Grande' },
            { 2: 'Selena Gomez' },
            { 3: 'Kylie Jenner' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Who scored the most goals in football?",
        correct: 2,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Lionel Messi' },
            { 1: 'Diego Maradona' },
            { 2: 'Pele' },
            { 3: 'Romário' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which team has the most Champions League trophies?",
        correct: 1,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'FC Barcelona' },
            { 1: 'Real Madrid' },
            { 2: 'AC Milan' },
            { 3: 'Bayern Munich' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Who has scored the most goals in a calendar year?",
        correct: 0,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Lionel Messi' },
            { 1: 'Cristiano Ronaldo' },
            { 2: 'Pele' },
            { 3: 'Kaka' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Who has scored a perfect hat trick?",
        correct: 3,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Lionel Messi' },
            { 1: 'Luis Suarez' },
            { 2: 'Zalatan' },
            { 3: 'Cristiano Ronaldo' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What team has scored the most Premier League goals?",
        correct: 2,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Liverpool' },
            { 1: 'Manchester City' },
            { 2: 'Manchester United' },
            { 3: 'Arsenal' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which Country won Most World Cup? ",
        correct: 1,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'France' },
            { 1: 'Brzail' },
            { 2: 'Italy' },
            { 3: 'Germany' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Who has taken the most wickets in World Cup cricket?",
        correct: 0,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Glenn McGrath' },
            { 1: 'Muttiah Muralitharan' },
            { 2: 'Wasim Akram' },
            { 3: 'Flintoff' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which Player has scored most runs in cricket?",
        correct: 2,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Sachin Tendulkar' },
            { 1: 'Graeme Hick' },
            { 2: 'Graham Gooch' },
            { 3: 'Kumar Sangakkara' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the chairman of ICC?",
        correct: 3,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Narayanaswami Srinivasan' },
            { 1: 'Manu Sawhney' },
            { 2: 'Jagmohan Dalmiya' },
            { 3: 'Shashank Manohar' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Who has won the most Euro cups?",
        correct: 0,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Germany' },
            { 1: 'Netherlands' },
            { 2: 'Portuga' },
            { 3: 'Greece' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Bayern munich highest goal scorer?",
        correct: 3,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Roland Wohlfarth' },
            { 1: 'Robert Lewandowski *' },
            { 2: 'Karl-Heinz Rummenigge' },
            { 3: 'Gerd Müller' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Who scored the most goals in Serie A?",
        correct: 1,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Francesco Totti' },
            { 1: 'Silvio Piola' },
            { 2: 'Gunnar Nordahl' },
            { 3: 'Giuseppe Meazza' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the richest league in the world?",
        correct: 2,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Serie A' },
            { 1: 'La Liga' },
            { 2: 'The Premier League ' },
            { 3: 'Bundesliga' },
        ]
    },
]


export default questions